searchexplorer.com 2011-09-17

# SearchExplorer : Contact Us

Overseas Internet Properties, Inc., owner and operator of SearchExplorer.com, has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding the collection and use of information submitted through our U.S. website, SearchExplorer.com (the "Site"). By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site. This Policy is the sole authorized statement of our practices concerning the collection, use and protection of personal information obtained through this Site.

We may update this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of material changes to this Policy by posting the updated Policy on this page. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by checking the "Effective Date of Current Policy" legend at the top of this Policy.

### Information Collection

We do not record any personal information through the Site. The Site does use tracking data and information obtained through cookies and other technologies to analyze visitor traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This data is not used to identify any specific visitor.

The Site monitors visitor traffic patterns by logging tracking data, which is collected automatically from each Site visitor. Tracking data may include information such as the IP address of the visitor's computer, its general geographic location, its browser type and operating system, the referring site, when the Site was visited and how much time was spent on the Site, which pages of the Site were visited and the order in which they were visited, which links were clicked, and past usage of the Site.

### Cookies

The Site may use "cookies" (small test files placed on a visitor's hard drive) and other technologies that allow us to recognize your browser when you visit the Site. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. You can visit the Site without accepting cookies. 

Additionally, we allow third parties to place ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. This policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or third parties.

### Third Party Websites

The Site contains links to other websites, including sites that we do not own or operate. Unless otherwise expressly stated, Overseas Internet Properties, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites' use of any information collected when Site visitors click through links to those sites. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policies of websites linked to the Site.

### Security

We take measures designed to prevent unauthorized intrusion to the Site and the alteration, acquisition or misuse of personal information. Unfortunately, however, no security system or system of transmitting data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be entirely secure. Thus, while we seek to protect your personal information, we cannot be responsible for loss, corruption, or unauthorized acquisition of personal information furnished to this Site or for any resulting damages.

### Offline v. Online Practices

This policy applies solely to our collection, use and disclosure of information obtained online through our Site, and does not apply to any of the practices conducted offline.

### The Way We Use and Disclose Information

We use tracking data and information obtained through cookies and other technologies to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Site, and to improve Site-related services and features. We also may share aggregated statistical data and other non-personally identifiable information with our current and potential business partners.

We work with third parties who provide services that may include, but are not necessarily limited to, website hosting, data processing and analysis, back-up and security services, and processing of credit card transactions. We may share personal information with these service providers for the purpose of providing these services. Although we seek to require these service providers to protect such personal information, and to use it only for the purpose for which it was provided, we cannot be responsible for third parties' violations of this Policy or of any other rights of visitors or consumers that use our Site.

We will provide personal information to law enforcement and other entities when we determine that such disclosure is required by subpoena, warrant, court order, or other applicable law or process.

We may provide personal information and other information collected online to a purchaser or successor entity in the event of a sale of our business or assets.
